Now it's probably time for you to make the code changes to your app.
والآن، ربما حان وقت إجراء تغييرات الكود في التطبيق.
Use the position parameter in that on item click method
استخدم معلمة الموقع في هذه الوظيفة OnItemClick
to figure out which word to play the pronunciation for.
للتعرف على الكلمة المطلوب تشغيل نطقها.
So I will tell you one syntax change that you'll need to make
ولذا، سأخبرك عن تغيير في تركيبة الكلمة الذي ستحتاج إجراؤه
to all your category activity files.
على جميع ملفات نشاط الفئة.
Now when you create the array list of words,
والآن وعند إنشاء قائمة مصفوفة الكلمات،
we'll need to add the word final in front of the declaration.
سنحتاج إلى إضافة الكلمة النهائية في مقدمة الإعلان.
And that way you can reference the words arraylist within the onItemClick method.
وبهذه الطريقة يمكنك الرجوع إلى قائمة مصفوفة الكلمات ضمن وظيفة onItemClick.
So that modification was a subtle detail required because of variable scope and
لذلك كان التعديل هو التفاصيل الدقيقة المطلوبة بسبب نطاق متغير
it's okay if you don't understand that just yet.
ولا بأس إذا لم تتفهم ذلك حتى الآن.
All that you need to know is when a clickListener is defined in line, so
كل ما تحتاج معرفته الآن أنه عند تحديد وظيفة clickListener في سطر،
here as an anonymous class,
يمكن التصنيف هنا على أنها فئة مجهولة،
its methods can only reference local variables if they are declared final.
ويمكن لطرقها أن تشير فقط إلى المتغيرات المحلية إذا تم الإعلان عنها في النهاية.
Or it can reference global variables in the NumbersActivity class.
أو قد تشير إلى المتغيرات العامة في فئة نشاط الأرقام.
So more details are included about this in the link below.
ولذا تم تضمين المزيد من التفاصيل عن ذلك في الرابط الوارد أدناه.
All right so go ahead and work on this coding task.
حسنًا، هيا بنا نمضي ونعمل في مهمة التشفير هذه.
It's expected that it'll take you a good amount of time so
من المتوقع أن تستغرق هذه المهمة بعض الوقت
be patient with yourself if you don't get it right away.
ولذا كن صبورًا، حتى تتمكن من الانتهاء منها.
There are also some hints below the quiz.
كما أن هناك بعض النصائح أسفل الاختبار.
But only use them if you get stuck.
ولكن استخدمها فقط إذا واجهتك مشكلة.
So to reiterate, for this task, within the NumbersActivity,
ولتكرار ذلك، مع تلك المهمة، ضمن نشاط الأرقام،
play the correct sound file for each word when it's clicked.
قم بتشغيل الملف الصوتي الصحيح لكل كلمة عند النقر فوقها.
And then repeat the same process for the other category activities.
ثم كرر الخطوة ذاتها لأنشطة الفئة الأخرى.
And then check this box when you're done.
ثم حدد هذا المربع عند الانتهاء.
So this is what your options look like when you're complete.
ستجد هذه الخيارات متاحة أمامك
Tap into numbers.
اضغط على الأرقام.
&gt;&gt; Booty.
&gt;&gt; بوتي.
&gt;&gt; Our good old Booty is working.
&gt;&gt; البوتي القديمة الرائعة تعمل.
Let's check out the other activities.
هيا بنا نتعرف على الأنشطة الأخرى.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[BLANK_AUDIO]
&gt;&gt; [INAUDIBLE] &gt;&gt; Nice.
&gt;&gt; [INAUDIBLE] &gt;&gt; رائع.
So see you on the other side.
أراكم مرة أخرى.